

# **TOM GIELIS**

Senior professional with 18 years of solid experience in Web Design & Development, Web Mastering, Graphic Design and a background in Animation, Web design and Multimedia. Currently in a WebDev training at Obelisk.

I worked for various web agencies and international companies in roles such as Webmaster, Graphic Designer, Front-end Developer, UI Designer. Mostly involved in Corporate digital transformations, content migrations, creation and content management of internal and external websites.

Service-oriented team player and creative problem solver with strong customer relationship skills, flexible, professional and committed to meet deadlines. A dynamic person who appreciates nice colleagues and a positive work atmosphere.

# **CLIENTS**

HP, Iomega, Gamma, The Belgian Post, Proximus, Sanoma Magazines, Veritas, Texaco, Multipharma, Bayer, Boerhinger Ingelheim, Philips/Douwe Egberts, Seat, Sony, Alcatel, Dexia, Kipling, Euronext, Bekaert,...

## **LANGUAGES**

- Dutch (native)
- English (very good)
- French (good)

# **CONTACT**



Lindberg 28-2520, Oelegem



+32 0474 49 17 59



tomgielis@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/tomgielis/

#### **EDUCATION**

1999 - 2000	Campus Vesalius, Leuven, Belgium Certificate
1996 - 1999	Audiovisual Arts & Animation Film Royal school of Fine arts, Gent, Belgium Bachelor degree of Arts (BA)
1992 - 1996	<b>Publicity &amp; Graphic Design</b> Karel de Grote Hogeschool, Antwerp, Belgium Bachelor degree of Arts (BA)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

01/20 - 09/20	<b>Obelisk - WebDev Training</b> Contact: Peter van den Heuvel, Danny Drijvers
2019 - 11/19	OMP - Senior Graphic Designer Contact: Maya Briels
2011 - 2019	Intrasoft International - Senior IT Consultant / Webmaster / DTP @REA (EC)  Contact: Lara Passante / Evangelos Tsavalopoulos
2010 - 2011	Despec Belgium - Webmaster / Designer Contact: Peter Delagaye
2006 - 2009	Digitopia - Art director / Content manager Contact: Jan Bussels
2004 - 2006	The Yellow Pages - Web Designer / Developer Contact: Wendy Van Dormael
2003 - 2004	<b>Mediamind - Web Designer / Animation Specialist</b> Contact: Ram Broeckaert
2001 - 2003	The reference - Web Designer / Developer / Animation Contact: Sofie Debals
2000 - 2001	The E-corporation (RIP) - Webdesigner / Animation Contact: Karen Peeters

#### **SKILLS**

Web mastering, Graphic Design, DTP, Content Management, Web Development, UI Design for websites and applications, Mailings, CMS (SharePoint / Drupal), SEO, Infographics, Animation, Style-guides/Visual ID, Presentations, Web analytics & statistics, Narrowcasting, Storyboarding,...

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, mySQL, WordPress, SEO, GIT, Emmet, SharePoint (CMS), Drupal (CMS), VS Code, Adobe CS (Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Animate,...)

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Patient • empathetic • sensitive • orderly • dedicated • integer • informative • organised • flexible • Interested in the latest technologies and eager to learn.